I think a lot of people listening to people in power, President, you, Secretary Blinken,
calling for a humanitarian pause, are asking themselves, why is that different from a ceasefire?
Two years ago, 2021, during an escalation of violence between Israel and Gaza,
you called for a ceasefire and you said you, quote, couldn't disagree more with Netanyahu's
policies, quote, when it came to the treatment of Palestinians. Is a ceasefire needed now?
I think it is, at least in the context of both sides agreeing. For example,
the release of those who have been kidnapped should be part of this, immediate release.
That should be the beginning of it. An effort should be made to engage in conversation between
the Israelis and the Palestinians. Let's face it, this has gone on for decades. Whatever the
rationale from the beginning, it has now reached an intolerable level. We need to have a resolution
in the Middle East that gives some promise for the future.
Have you told the president, the White House, you think it's time for a ceasefire? Because that
is a word that the president is intentionally not using.
Well, believe me, what I said earlier about ceasefires under circumstances, for example,
the release of those who have been kidnapped as part of it, an indication that this is a good
faith effort on the part of the other side. But no, I've not communicated with the White House on that.
Well, they heard you now. Senator Lindsey Graham on CNN this week.
He is here.